Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 5 and District 5 Locals, 1936-1983 UE.4.1.5
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 5, 1.
  - District 5 Correspondence and Report, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - J. Hurley to UE Regarding Local 530, December 11, 1952; 3.
    - Jean Pare Report to Peace Congress, December 12, 1952; 4.
  - District 5 Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Macus and Feiner Regarding Local 513 Disbanding with December 23, 1952, Emspak Letter to C.S. Jackson (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - District 5 Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Social Security in Canada, January 1953; 1.
    - Karen Morlen Speech, February 21, 1953; 2.
    - Brief on Bill 93 with February 24, 1953, C.S. Jackson Letter to Trade Unionists, February 18, 1953; 3.
  - District 5 Miscellaneous, 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Contract Between GE and UE, November 13, 1954; 1.
    - James Matles to David Ratner, December 2, 1954; 2.
    - UE Clear Water Lodge, March 9, 1955; 3.
    - Brief Regarding Female Employees Act, March 23, 1955; 4.
  - District 5 Miscellaneous, 1955, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Reduced Hours District Council Report, June 25, 1955; 1.
    - Ross Cain to UE Regarding Philco Strike and Factionalism, 2.
  - District 5 Miscellaneous, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Pledge Card Regarding Organization, n.d.; 1.
    - David McDonald to James Carey Regarding Steelworkers Organizing Committee, n.d.; 2.
    - Summary of Cost of Living Order, n.d.; 3.
    - Organization Summary, n.d.; 4.
    - District Executive Board Statement on the War, n.d.; 5.
  - District 5 Miscellaneous, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Appendix A Regarding Wage and Prices, 1.
    - Summing Up Discussion Regarding Political Action, n.d.; 2.
    - Veterans Welfare Committee Report, n.d.; 3.
  - District 5 Miscellaneous, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Report on Campaign to Amend PC 1003, 1.
    - Canadian Resolution Regarding Autonomy, n.d.; 2.
    - Jackson Letter Regarding Dues, n.d.; 3.
    - J. Marsh Report, n.d.; 4.
    - Labor Needs All-In Trade Unions Unity Regarding Canadian Congress of Labour and Trades and Labour Congress of Canada Merger, 5.
    - N. Hamblin to Charles Daley Regarding Stewart Warner Organization, n.d.; 6.
  - District 5 B.C. Lumber Workers Newspaper, October 6-20, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - District 5 The Brass Man Newspaper, February 13-27, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - District 5 The Erie County Press Newspaper, June 26-July 17, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - District 5 Steward's Bulletin Newspaper, July-August 1953, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - District 5 UE Facts Newspaper, March 25-June 10, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - District 5 UE Facts Newspaper, August 12-November 25, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - District 5 UE Facts Newspaper, February 10, 1948-September 7, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - District 5 UE Facts Newspaper, November 29-December 15, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - District 5 UE News Newspaper, June 12, 1941-April 4, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - District 5 UE News Newspaper, April 11-August 15, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - District 5 Evening Examiner Newspaper, July 5, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - District 5 Canadian Woodworkers Newspaper, December 15, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - District 5 Pamphlets, 1941-1949 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Can This Have Happened in Canada, September 13, 1941; 1.
    - Conference Call, June 1, 1941; 2.
    - The Labor Relations Act, 1949; 3.
    - ...Welfare of the Congress, May 1949; 4.
    - Communication Against Rarders, December 2, 1949; 5.
  - District 5 Pamphlets, 1952-1954, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - How the Steel Staff Broke the Strike at Warden King Montreal, October 27, 1952; 1.
    - It's A Crime, January 1953; 2.
    - We Were Northern Electric Workers!, 1953; 3.
    - Report of District Officers, Feburary 27-March 1, 1954; 4.
    - The Canadian UE Steward, September-October 1954; 5.
    - Join UE-CIO to Win a Real Salary Increase, n.d.; 6.
    - The Five Points of AWSE Leaders vs. The Five Points of UE-CIO, n.d.; 7.
    - An Urgent Message, n.d.; 8.
    - Canadian General Electric Employees! You are the Interested Victims!, n.d.; 9.
    - Industrial Disputes Investigated Act, 10.
  - District 5 Leaflets, 1942-1953, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - "The UE-In Time of War", June 13, 1942; 1.
    - "Honeywell Local to Quit C.I.O. for A.F.L. Teamsters", February 24, 1953; 2.
    - "U.E. Bulletin", n.d.; 3.
    - "In Defense of Collective Bargaining", 4.
    - "I Defend Collective Bargaining Petition", 5.
    - "Company Unions", n.d.; 6.
    - The Canadian Tribune, "Victory Labour", n.d.; 7.
    - "Conference to Secure the Release of C.S. Jackson", n.d.; 8.
  - District 5 Leaflets, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - "No. 1 on the Right to Organize", n.d.; 1.
    - "No. 2 on the Boss Says", n.d.; 2.
    - "No. 3 on the Workers Says", n.d.; 3.
    - "No. 4 on the Government Stipulates", n.d.; 4.
    - "No. 5 on How to Vote", n.d.; 5.
    - "No. 6 on 7 Reasons for a Vote of Strike", n.d.; 6.
    - "No. 7 on Your Choice" with Sample Ballot, n.d.; 7.
    - "Final Voting Instructions", n.d.; 8.
    - "Sample Ballot", n.d.; 9.
    - "New Office Location in Toronto", n.d.; 10.
    - "Change of Address Cards", n.d.; 11.
    - "An Open Letter to CGE Employees", n.d.; 12.
    - "The Otis-Fensom Organizer", n.d.; 13.
  - District 5 Press Releases, 1943-1948 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - War Production, May 1943; 1.
    - Local 512 Willard Storage Battery Contract, September 1943; 2.
    - Small Arms Layoff, August 20, 1945; 3.
    - Statement on the Rand Formula Settlement of the Ford Strike, January 31, 1946; 4.
    - Canadian Congress Strike and Striking Unions, August 6, 1946; 5.
    - Canada Wire Cable Co. Strike, August 15, 1946; 6.
    - Authorized Strike Vote in Toronto GE Plants, June 4, 1947; 7.
    - Protests Police Attitude at Rogers Picket Line, February 25, 1948; 8.
    - Vote for Change of Union Results Negative, June 21, 1948; 9.
    - Locals 507, 515, and 516 Davenport Workers, Royce Ave. Works, and War Street Carboloy, June 25, 1948; 10.
    - Local 521 Leaside Rogers Majestic Radio Meeting on Strike Breaking, August 25, 1948; 11.
  - District 5 Press Releases, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Seizure of C.S. Jackson by U.S. Immigration, September 8, 1948; 1.
    - Dominion Electric Protection Co. Strike, September 9, 1948; 2.
    - Concerning 'Secret' Meeting of Ontario Federation of Labour, April 1, 1949; 3.
    - Government Must Prosecute Shotgun Artists, April 8, 1949; 4.
    - Canadian General Electric Co. Negotiations, October 14, 1949; 5.
    - Canadian General Electric Co. Strike, October 17, 1949; 6.
    - Protests of Rent Increases by UE and All Other Community Groups, November 4, 1949; 7.
    - Independence of UE from Canadian Congress of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, November 4, 1949; 8.
    - Prevention of Splitting Labor's Ranks, November 30, 1949; 9.
    - "UE Members Beat Bank Raids and Continue to Lead in Economic Gains", December 5, 1949; 10.
    - Per Capita Payments, December 5, 1949
  - District 5 Press Releases, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Canadian General Electric Co. Toronto and Peterboro Contracts, May 2, 1953; 1.
    - Social Security, January 23, 1953; 2.
    - "CGE and Westinghouse UE Members Meet to Map Policy" Regarding Coming Negotiations and "Renewal of UE Contracts with Trane Co. of Canada", January 29, 1953; 3.
    - Local 520 Hoover Co. Contract, February 6, 1953; 4.
    - Local 520 Brown Baggs Foundry Co. Contract, February 17, 1953; 5.
    - Canadian General Electric, Westinghouse, Canada Wire & Cable, and Ferranti Electric Negotiations, February 23, 1953; 6.
    - Local 512 Square D Settlement and Local 517 Provincial Gas Settlement, March 6, 1953; 7.
  - District 5 Press Releases, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Canadian General Electric Co. Negotiation, March 12, 1953; 1.
    - Canadian General Electric Negotiation and Local 521 Canada Wire & Cable Contract, March 31, 1953; 2.
    - Local 523 Reliance Electric Contract, April 15, 1953; 3.
    - Entry Visa Refusal, April 30, 1953; 4.
    - Peace Time Production on St. Lawrence Seaway, May 1, 1953; 5.
    - Local 520 Aervox Co. Contract, May 12, 1953; 6.
    - International Unions Discuss Full Employment in Peace Time, June 11, 1953; 7.
    - Desertion of Unions by Jack Osborne, July 6, 1953; 8.
    - Construction of All Canadian Pipeline, November 3, 1953; 9.
    - Westinghouse Service Plant, Etobicoke, and A.C. Wickman Contracts, November 20, 1953; 10.
    - Local 514 Amalgamated Electric Corporation Contract, November 27, 1953; 11.
    - Support of Canadian Seaman, December 30, 1953; 12.
  - District 5 Press Releases, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - United Action with Trade Unions Centers in Quebec, January 26, 1954; 1.
    - District Council Meeting, January 27, 1954; 2.
    - Support for Soviet Union Trade Deal with British Industry, February 5, 1954; 3.
    - Advocation of All-Canadian Seaway, February 8, 1954; 4.
    - Unemployment, February 26, 1954; 5.
    - Advocation of All-Canadian Seaway, May 11, 1954; 6.
    - Local 521 Canada Wire & Cable Co. Contract and Pension Plan, June 4, 1954; 7.
    - Importation of Electrical Products into Canada, June 21, 1954; 8.
    - St. Lawrence Seaway, Opposition of UE to Wiley Bill, July 6, 1954; 9.
    - Opposition to U.S. Control of Section of Seaway, August 16, 1954; 10.
    - Opposition to Government Interference in Collective Bargaining, August 16, 1954; 11.
  - District 5 Press Releases, 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Canadian General Electric Co. Strike, October 28, 1954; 1.
    - All General Electric Plants Covered by UE Contract, November 17, 1954; 2.
    - International Resistance Co. Strike, November 3, 1954; 3.
    - Guelph Works Negotiation, November 22, 1954; 4.
    - Guelph Works and CGE Negotiations, December 16, 1954; 5.
    - Local 514 Canadian Electrical Resistors Negotiation, January 4, 1955; 6.
    - Critisicm of the Knox Report on Problems of Industry, February 1, 1955; 7.
  - District 5 Press Releases, C.S. Jackson Comment on the Analysis of Problems of Industry By and Representative of a USA Corporation Operating in Canada, February 18, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - District 5 Press Releases, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Rejection of Involvement in USA War Adventures, March 15, 1955; 1.
    - Female Employees Fair Renumeration Act, March 23, 1955; 2.
    - Employment, March 28, 1955; 3.
    - Canadian General Electric Guelph Works Negotiation, March 31, 1955; 4.
    - Unemployment Benefits, May 26, 1955; 5.
    - Contracts Demand 35-Hour Work Week and Increased Take-home Pay Negotiations, June 27, 1955; 6.
    - Examination of Incentive Systems and Combat Excessive Work Loads, September 19, 1955; 7.
    - Backing of General Motors Workers by UE, September 20, 1955; 8.
    - Investigation Demands of Working Conditions of Teenaged Girls in the Television Industry, October 7, 1955; 9.
    - Local 512 Delamere Williams, Local 514 J & J Taylor Co., and Local 514 Diamonk State Fibre Contracts, October 7, 1955; 10.
    - Local 521 Canada Wire & Cable Co. Strike, December 1, 1955; 11.
    - Canada Wire & Cable Co. Strike, December 11, 1955; 12.
    - Pay Bonus for Regular Pickets, Local 521, and Canada Wire & Cable, December 15, 1955; 13.
    - Labor Unity with United Steelworkers and Canada Wire & Cable Strikes, December 16, 1955; 14.
    - Local 521 and Canada Wire & Cable Negotiation, December 19, 1955; 15.
    - Local 521 and Canada Wire & Cable Strike, December 22, 1955; 16.
  - District 5 Press Releases, 1956 - 1966 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - District 5 Press Releases, 1951 - 1957 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - District 5 Press Releases, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - District 5 Press Releases, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - District 5 Press Releases, 1979 - 1982 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - District 5 Press Releases, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - District 5 Newspaper Clippings, 1940-1941, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - "Socialism a Reality in England, He Says," Toronto Daily Star, May 27, 1940; 1.
    - "Can This Have Happened in Canada?" Toronto Daily Star, 2.
    - "Given More Facts on Jackson Inquiry," Toronto Daily Star, September 15, 1941; 3.
    - "The Jailing of Reid Robinson," Toronto Daily Star, October 11, 1941; 4.
    - "A Prebytery Rebukes the Government," Toronto Daily Star, October 15, 1941; 5.
    - "Labor Leaders Support Move on War Effort", n.d.; 6.
    - "CIO Plans to Expel Three Red Unions, CCL Oficial Says", n.d.; 7.
    - "CGE Workers Delay M. Larty in Appointment", n.d.; 8.
    - "Name Jackson Successor," Toronto Daily Star, n.d.; 9.
    - "Progress is Made in CGE Dispute", n.d.; 10.
    - "Women Scream as Police, Strikers Clash Here", n.d.; 11.
    - "Soldiers Break Picket Line Won't Do It Again," Toronto Daily Star, n.d.; 12.
    - "...Plan a Challenge to GE, Westinghouse", n.d.; 13.
    - "Support of Citizens is Sought by United Electrical Workers," Peterboro Examiner, n.d.; 14.
- District 5 Locals, 2.
  - Local 504
    - Local 504 Incoming Correspondence, 1937-1951 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Peter Abbondi to Frank E. Krouse Regarding Request of Westinghouse Agreement Copies and Notification of Sending Copies of the Comparison, November 28, 1950; 1.
      - Bill Cohn to William Walsh Regarding Officers and Photos Sent, March 23, 1950; 2.
      - Cohn to Stan Roberson Regarding Advice on Issuing a Shop Paper, August 1, 1951; 3.
      - James Carey to R. McClure Regarding Comment on Proposed Departmental Activity Program and Acknowledged Sending of 500 Applications Blanks, May 14, 1937; 4.
      - Carey to Joseph Latham Regarding Support Given for Appointment of Full Time Organizer, May 29, 1937; 5.
      - Walton Criscuolo to Frank Krause Regarding Machine Maintenance, April 26, 1949; 6.
      - Julius Emspak to McClure Regarding Check Enclosed for Bills, Support for Idea of Organizing Committees, and Receipt of Charter for Thor Canadian Co., April 20, 1937; 7.
      - Emspak to McClure Regarding Encouragement in Organizing Work of Westinghouse Locals, April 29, 1937; 8.
      - Emspak to McClure Regarding Check Enclosed and Names Included for Mailing List for the People's Press, May 7, 1937; 9.
      - Emspak to McClure Regarding Approval of Activity of Jackson and Plans for Aid in Working Out Program in Future, May 25, 1937; 10.
      - Emspak to McClure Regarding Union Opposition by Crocker Wheeler Co. and Discussion of Pamphlets, May 26, 1937; 11.
      - Emspak to George Orban Regarding Enclosed Initiation Stamps, Clarification of Per Capita Tax, and Promise of Placement of Full-time Organizer, May 28, 1937; 12.
      - Emspak to McClure Regarding Receipts, Application Cards, and Organizational Work at Robbins-Myers Plant, June 2, 1937; 13.
      - Emspak to Orban Regarding Enclosed Receipt and Per Capita Payment, June 5, 1937; 14.
      - Emspak to Orban Regarding Dues Books and Enclosed Receipts, Stamps and Application Card, June 11, 1937; 15.
      - Emspak to Latham Regarding Request for Money Order or Checks as Opposed to Canadian Currency for Payments, June 16, 1937; 16.
      - Emspak to McClure Regarding Receipts, Money Order Fees, and Request to Contact Amalgamated Clothing Workers, June 17, 1937; 17.
      - Emspak to McClure Regarding Enclosed Check, Support for Tactics in Publicizing the Union, and Acceptance of Machinist Locals Disaffiliating from the American Federation of Labor, June 17, 1937; 18.
      - Emspak to McClure Regarding Enclosed Check and Receipts, Application Forms, Money Order Fees, and Request to Contact Amalgamated Clothing Workers, July 17, 1937; 19.
      - Emspak to Orban Regarding Acknowledged Payment of Initiations, Sending of Additional Initiation Stamps, and Explanation of Procedure for Member Payment, June 18, 1937; 20.
      - Emspak to McClure Regarding Receipts, Enclosed Check, Jackson Sent as Organizer, Advice to Meet with Jackson, and Discussion of Organizational Program in Canada, July 14, 1937; 21.
      - Emspak to McClure Regarding Jackson as Main Organizer in Canada and Meeting with Jackson, July 28, 1937; 22.
      - Emspak to Local 504 Regarding Enclosed Additional Stamps, August 5, 1937; 23.
      - Emspak to Orban Regarding Confirmation for May Receipts, Stamps, and Per Capita Payment Acknowledged, August 5, 1937; 24.
    - Local 504 Incoming Correspondence, 1937-1952 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Julius Emspak to Robert McClure Regarding Enclosed Check and People's Press Order, August 30, 1937; 1.
      - Emspak to McClure Regarding Enclosed Check and Forthcoming Matles Letter, October 1, 1937; 2.
      - Emspak to George Orban Regarding Initiation Stamps and Distribution of Unemployment Stamps, December 2, 1937; 3.
      - Emspak to Orban Regarding Enclosed Receipts, December 14, 1937; 4.
      - Emspak to McClure Regarding Enclosed Check, December 31, 1937; 5.
      - Emspak to McClure Regarding Enclosed Check and Compliment on Work Done, January 6, 1938; 6.
      - Emspak to Orban Regarding Request for Payment, January 11, 1938; 7.
      - Emspak to Orban Regarding Request for Checks, January 25, 1938; 8.
      - Emspak to McClure Regarding Issuance of Union Light, April 5, 1938; 9.
      - Emspak to Orban Regarding Payment Due, April 12, 1938; 10.
      - Emspak to Orban Regarding Payment Due, June 23, 1938; 11.
      - Emspak to McClure Regarding Mailing List for Subscriptions of People's Press, June 23, 1938; 12.
      - Emspak to McClure Regarding Charter, June 26, 1939; 13.
      - Emspak to Frank Krouse Regarding Bonding, December 11, 1946; 14.
      - Emspak to Krouse, December 14, 1948; 15.
      - Emspak to Malcolm Dougan Regarding Bonding, March 9, 1949; 16.
      - Emspak to Ernest Sartain Regarding Enclosed Check, April 8, 1952; 17.
      - Nat Geller to George Harris Regarding Convention Officers, September 2, 1941; 18.
      - Joseph Latham to James Carey Regarding Westinghouse Locals Meeting Schedule, August 24, 1937; 19.
      - James Matles to Latham Regarding Organizer Jackson Handling Local Difficulties, July 8, 1937; 20.
      - Matles to Latham Regarding Appointment of Jackson as Organizer, July 13, 1937; 21.
      - Matles to McClure Regarding Support of Jackson as Organizer, August 4, 1937; 22.
      - Matles to Daniel MacLean Regarding Copy of Letter to McClure, Arrival of Matles in Canada, and Request for Payment, October 5, 1937; 23.
      - Matles to McClure Regarding Preparation to File Suit Against International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, April 14, 1939; 24.
      - William Walsh to Matthews Regarding Pension Supplement at Local 610, March 2, 1950; 25.
      - Unsigned Letter to Orban Regarding Receipts and Enclosed Initiation Stamps, May 19, 1937; 26.
    - Local 504 Outgoing Correspondence, 1937-1955, undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - T. Campbell to Ed Matthews Regarding Enclosed Check, November 20, 1951; 1.
      - Campbell to Julius Emspak Regarding Enclosed Check, August 29, 1952; 2.
      - W.C. Carlson to Emspak Regarding Enclosed Check, Dues, and Stamps, 3.
      - George Harris to Emspak Regarding Bank Deposit Slip, April 8, 1947; 4.
      - August Hein to Emspak Regarding Enclosed Application, March 16, 1937; 5.
      - Frank Krouse to Emspak Regarding Bonding, December 13, 1948; 6.
      - Krouse to Matthews Regarding Copies of Westinghouse Electric Agreement, November 22, 1950; 7.
      - Krouse to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Request for Information on Union Operations, November 2, 1955; 8.
      - Joseph Latham to James Carey Regarding Need of Full Time Organizer, May 25, 1937; 9.
      - Latham to Carey Regarding Full Time Organizer, June 26, 1937; 10.
      - Latham to Emspak Regarding Compensation for Loss of Position, June 29, 1937; 11.
      - Latham to Local 504 Regarding Dues Stamps, August 1, 1937; 12.
      - Matthews to Local 504 Regarding Negotiation Support, n.d.; 13.
      - Robert McClure to Julius Emspak Regarding Charter Installation, April 9, 1937; 14.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding People's Press, April 29, 1937; 15.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Union Membership Drive, May 7, 1937; 16.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Meetings and Application Cards, May 16, 1937; 17.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Money Order and Enclosed Application Cards, May 25, 1937; 18.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Money Order and Brautford Washing Machine Co. Charter, June 4, 1937; 19.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Enclosed Bills, Union Events, and Election of Officers, June 14, 1937; 20.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Money Orders, Firing at Union Activities, Postponement of Elections, and Received Check, June 21, 1937; 21.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Firing of Union Members, June 28, 1937; 22.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Firing of Union Members, July 8, 1937; 23.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Order Received, Hein Jackson's Help on Firing Situation, and Conference Planned by Jackson, July 18, 1937; 24.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Enclosed Bills and Planned Campaign, August 1, 1937; 25.
      - McClure to James Matles Regarding Bills, August 23, 1937; 26.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Bills, Burkhart, Jackson Attending Meeting, and McClure as Local Organizer for Local 504, September 1, 1937; 27.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Bills and Recommendation of Discontinued Paper, September 18, 1937; 28.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Matles Discussion on Bookkeeping System, December 27, 1937; 29.
    - Local 504 Outgoing Correspondence, 1937-1938, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - Robert McClure to Julius Emspak Regarding Elected Officers, March 31, 1938; 1.
      - McClure to People's Press Regarding Order, June 12, 1938; 2.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Bill for People's Press, June 12, 1938; 3.
      - McClure to James Matles Regarding Pamphlet Sent by National Electric Products and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Boycott, April 15, 1939; 4.
      - McClure to Emspak Regarding Charter and Headway with Local Steel Plant, June 18, 1939; 5.
      - George Orban to Emspak Regarding Requests for Stamps, Explanation of Per Capita, Payments, and Setting Up New Loads, May 25, 1939; 6.
      - Orban to Emspak Regarding Request for Initiation Rules for Dues, June 1, 1939; 7.
      - Orban to Emspak Regarding Enclosed Money Orders and Request for Application Form, June 5, 1939; 8.
      - Orban to Emspak Regarding Initiation Procedures, June 12, 1937; 9.
      - Orban to Emspak Regarding New Members Listed for Publication, June 12, 1937; 10.
      - Orban to Emspak Regarding Receipt of Stamps and Financial Reports, June 30, 1937; 11.
      - Orban to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 3, 1937; 12.
      - Orban to Emspak Regarding Finances and Initiation Stamps, August 14, 1937; 13.
      - Orban to Emspak Regarding Financial Report, November 20, 1937; 14.
      - Orban to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Mailing List, December 9, 1937; 15.
      - Orban to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 12, 1938; 16.
      - Orban to Local 504 Regarding Notice of Due Payments, July 18, 1939; 17.
      - Orban to Emspak Regarding Finances, n.d.; 18.
    - Local 504 Outgoing Correspondence, 1942-1953 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - Alfred Ready to George Drew Regarding Support of Industry Labor Conference, May 13, 1942; 1.
      - Ready to James Matles Regarding Election Support, April 26, 1950; 2.
      - Stan Roberson to UE News Regarding Shop Paper, July 17, 1951; 3.
      - Roberson to Julius Emspak Regarding Check Enclosed, September 1, 1953; 4.
      - Lillian Smith to Emspak Regarding Veterans, February 13, 1945; 5.
      - Bob Ward to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, September 29, 1943; 6.
    - Local 504 Salary and Expense Letters, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 47)
      - Robert McClure, July 21, 1937; 1.